<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>avimehenwal</title>
    <link>https://avimehenwal.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on avimehenwal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://avimehenwal.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>cPingProbe perl tool</title>
      <link>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/cpingprobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/cpingprobe/</guid>
      <description>cPingProbe perl tool Summary cPingProbe is a multiplatform (Windows, Linux, mac OS, Solaris) multi host pinging tool that would continuously record your RTT from pinging machine and would notify on any discrepancy from normal trend. Its a great resource friendly tool that would do it task without starving other application of system resources. Currently it supports 3 protocol methods to test host round trip time. TCP(default) , ICMP(standard) and UDP(generally not recommended for long term analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addabol webapp</title>
      <link>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/addabol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/addabol/</guid>
      <description>Addabol Backend developer and Release engineer
Server side programmer for webApp name addabol (later renamed to planito). WebApp is now deprecated.
 writing web services on pyramid and database APIs deploying the application on AWS infrastructure data and web scraping for user data  AWS, pyramid, Facebook Graph API, Bitbucket, Gevent
Facebook | on Amazon | Google+</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dockerised Python Webapp</title>
      <link>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/dockerised-python-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 16:25:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avimehenwal.in/projects/dockerised-python-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Dockerised python webapp A dockerised python webapplication build to demonstrate the ease of deployment within containers and speeding up release process.
https://github.com/avimehenwal/cherrypy-app</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://avimehenwal.in/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avimehenwal.in/contact/</guid>
      <description>For long-term projects related quotes and queries please contact me on my LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://avimehenwal.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avimehenwal.in/about/</guid>
      <description>Software Automation profession who treats automation as a software development project and believes thoroughly tested products is not a choice but a mandate. Testing is an activity, not a team. New challenging tasks involving Research and Development have always fascinated me.
Professional started working as a network automation engineer, Application Developer and Software Automation Engineer and currently freelancing on testing, DevOps projects.
 Working environments Scrum, Agile, CI/CD, continuous delivery Specialties Linux, Automation, Python, lua, shell, TDD, pen testing Domains Interested Distributed Systems and Operations, Cloud Computing, System Architecture, OS Virtualization, Machine Learning and Secutities  Please contact via LinkedIn for work realted queries and my rates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>